A '60s radical. An uptight fed. It's gonna be a real trip!
Flashback is a action, comedy, crime film directed by Franco Amurri.
A hippie radical, Huey Walker has been a fugitive for decades,
accused of a crime that he may not have committed.
Finally apprehended, Walker is escorted to trial by
uptight 20-something FBI agent John Buckner.
While the two seem to be polar opposites, it turns out that Buckner may have more in common with Walker than is
initially apparent, a point that is driven home when the pair faces off against a sinister small-town sheriff.
Huey Walker, played by Dennis Hopper.
John Buckner, played by Kiefer Sutherland.
Maggie, played by Carol Kane.
Stark, played by Paul Dooley.
Sheriff Rand Hightower, played by Cliff DeYoung.
Barry, played by Richard Masur.
Flashback is a 1990 American adventure comedy film starring
Dennis Hopper, Kiefer Sutherland, and Carol Kane.
The film is written by David Loughery and directed by Franco Amurri.
The film explores themes of hippie, yuppie, fbi, lsd, fake identity.
The tone is lighthearted.